Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0172, 1 fragment 04 x 6 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0172)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0173, 1 fragment 20 x 4 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0173)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0174, 1 fragment 07 x 4 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0174)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0175, 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0175)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0176, 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0176)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0177, 1 fragment 09.5 x 9 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0177)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0178, 1 fragment 06 x 6 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0178)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0179, 1 fragment 09.5 x 15 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0179)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0180, 1 fragment 07.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0180)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0181, 1 fragment 07.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0181)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0182, 1 fragment 04.5 x 9.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0182)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0183, 1 fragment 01 x 3 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0183)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0184, 1 fragment 05 x 6 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0184)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0185, 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0185)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0186, 1 fragment 08.5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0186)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0187.01, 2 fragments 04.5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0187.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0187.02, 2 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0187.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0188, 1 fragment 06 x 5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0188)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0189, 1 fragment 06.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0189)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0190, 1 fragment 06 x 5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0190)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0191, 1 fragment 03 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0191)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0192, 1 fragment 05 x 6 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0192)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0193, 1 fragment 09.5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0193)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0194, 1 fragment 10.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 3, Item P.NYU inv 0194)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0195, 1 fragment 10.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0195)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0196, 1 fragment 02.5 x 4 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0196)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0197, 1 fragment 05.5 x 15.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0197)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0198, 1 fragment 04.5 x 5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0198)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0199, 1 fragment 06.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0199)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0200, 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0200)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0201, 1 fragment 09.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0201)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0202, 1 fragment 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0202)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0203, 1 fragment 03 x 7 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0203)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0204, 1 fragment 07.5 x 3 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0204)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0205, 1 fragment 08.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0205)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0206, 1 fragment 03 x 5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0206)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0207, 1 fragment 02 x 5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0207)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0208, 1 fragment 26 x 11.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0208)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0209, 1 fragment 07.0 x 18.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0209)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0210, 1 fragment 05.5 x 14 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0210)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0211, 1 fragment 16 x 8 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0211)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0212, 1 fragment 13 x 5.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0212)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0213, 1 fragment 10.0 x 15.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0213)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0214, 1 fragment 05.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0214)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0215, 1 fragment 06 x 7 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0215)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0216, 1 fragment 05.5 x 9 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0216)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0217, 1 fragment 06.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0217)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0218, 1 fragment 11.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0218)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0219, 1 fragment 11.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0219)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0220, 1 fragment 12 x 7 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0220)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0221, 1 fragment 05 x 7 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0221)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0222, 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0222)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0223, 1 fragment 08.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0223)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0224, 1 fragment 08 x 4 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0224)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0225, 1 fragment 06 x 06 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0225)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0226, 1 fragment 10 x 5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0226)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0227, 1 fragment 06 x 4.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0227)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0228, 1 fragment 03.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0228)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0229, 1 fragment 03 x 08.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0229)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0230, 1 fragment 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0230)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0231, 1 fragment 06 x 6.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0231)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0232, 1 fragment 06.5 x 7 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0232)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0233, 1 fragment 06 x 4.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0233)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0234, 1 fragment 10 x 3.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0234)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0235, 1 fragment 13 x 4 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0235)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0236, 1 fragment 04 x 4 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0236)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0237, 1 fragment 04 x 3 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0237)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0238, 1 fragment 03.5 x 4 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0238)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0239, 1 fragment 04 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0239)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0240, 1 fragment 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0240)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0241, 1 fragment 03 x 7 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0241)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0242, 1 fragment 02.5 x 6 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0242)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0243, 1 fragment 04 x 2 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0243)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0244, 1 fragment 03 x 5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0244)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0245.01, 1 fragment 01 x 2 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0245.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0245.02, 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0245.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0245.03, 1 fragment 00.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0245.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0246, 1 fragment 06.5 x 2 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0246)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0247, 1 fragment 09 x 3 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0247)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0248, 1 fragment 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0248)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0249, 1 fragment 05 x 2 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0249)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0250, 1 fragment 04 x 7 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0250)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0251, 1 fragment 07.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0251)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0252, 1 fragment 07.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0252)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0253, 1 fragment 02 x 4 cm (Box 4, Item P.NYU inv 0253)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0254, 1 fragment 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0254)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0255, 1 fragment 06.5 x 4 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0255)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0256, 1 fragment 05.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0256)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0257, 1 fragment 03.5 x 6 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0257)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0258, 1 fragment 09.5 x 2 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0258)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0259, 1 fragment 03 x 3 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0259)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0260, 1 fragment 05.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0260)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0261, 1 fragment 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0261)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0262, 1 fragment 02 x 03 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0262)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0263, 1 fragment 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0263)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0264, 1 fragment 04.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0264)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0265, 1 fragment 03.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0265)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0266, 1 fragment 05 x 2 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0266)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0267, 1 fragment 06 x 2 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0267)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0268, 1 fragment 04.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0268)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0269, 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0269)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0270, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0270)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0271, 1 fragment 04.5 x 2 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0271)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0272, 1 fragment 05 x 1 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0272)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0273, 1 fragment 04 x 1 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0273)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0274, 1 fragment 15.5 x 3 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0274)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0275, 1 fragment 08.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0275)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0276, 1 fragment 04 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0276)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0277, 1 fragment 08.5 x 3 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0277)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0278, 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0278)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0279, 1 fragment 12.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0279)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0280, 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0280)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0281, 1 fragment 04.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0281)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0282, 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0282)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0283, 1 fragment 03.5 x 6 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0283)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0284, 1 fragment 03.5 x 7 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0284)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0285, 1 fragment 02.x 7 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0285)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0286, 1 fragment 01.5 x 16.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0286)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0287, 1 fragment 04.5 x 4 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0287)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0288, 1 fragment 03 x 6 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0288)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0289, 1 fragment 03.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0289)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0290, 1 fragment 04 x 5.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0290)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0291, 1 fragment 07.5 x 6 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0291)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0292, 1 fragment 05.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0292)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0293, 1 fragment 04.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0293)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0294.01, 2 fragments 04.5 x 5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0294.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0294.02, 2 fragments 02.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0294.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0295, 1 fragment 06.5 x 3 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0295)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0296, 1 fragment 10.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0296)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0297, 1 fragment 07.5 x 4 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0297)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0298, 1 fragment 08 x 4 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0298)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0299, 1 fragment 04.5 x 3 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0299)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0300, 1 fragment 15 x 4.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0300)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0301, 1 fragment 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0301)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0302, 1 fragment 13 x 5.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0302)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0303, 1 fragment 14 x 8 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0303)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0304, 1 fragment 14 x 11 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0304)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0305, 1 fragment 01 x 7 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0305)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0306, 1 fragment 05 x 4 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0306)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0307, 1 fragment 05.5 x 4 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0307)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0308, 1 fragment 02 x 10 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0308)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0309, 1 fragment 08.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0309)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0310, 1 fragment 06 x 8 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0310)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0311, 1 fragment 04.5 x 3 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0311)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0312, 1 fragment 07 x 7 cm (Box 5, Item P.NYU inv 0312)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0313, 1 fragment 06 x 9.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0313)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0314, 1 fragment 09.5 x 4 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0314)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0315, 1 fragment 04 x 9 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0315)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0316, 1 fragment 12.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0316)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0317, 1 fragment 06.5 x 4 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0317)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0318, 1 fragment 08.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0318)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0319, 1 fragment 04 x 12.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0319)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0320, 1 fragment 11 x 8 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0320)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0321, 1 fragment 16.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0321)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0322.01, 1 fragment 11 x 7.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0322.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0322.02, 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0322.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0323, 1 fragment 07.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0323)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0324, 1 fragment 08 x 4.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0324)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0325, 1 fragment 17 x 7 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0325)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0326, 1 fragment 11.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0326)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0327, 1 fragment 11 x 5.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0327)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0328, 1 fragment 08.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0328)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0329, 1 fragment 16.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0329)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0330, 1 fragment 06.5 x 10 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0330)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0331, 1 fragment 10 x 5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0331)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0332, 1 fragment 07.0 x 15.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0332)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0333, 1 fragment 08 x 6.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0333)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0334, 1 fragment 25.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0334)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0335, 1 fragment 10.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0335)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0336, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0336)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0337, 1 fragment 12.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0337)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0338, 1 fragment 08.5 x 6 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0338)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0339, 1 fragment 12.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0339)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0340, 1 fragment 12.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0340)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0341, 1 fragment 11 x 2.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0341)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0342, 1 fragment 06 x 3.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0342)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0343, 1 fragment 07 x 3 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0343)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0344, 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0344)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0345, 1 fragment 05 x 6.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0345)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0346, 1 fragment 06 x 5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0346)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0347, 1 fragment 02.5 x 17 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0347)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0348, 1 fragment 03.5 x 2 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0348)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0349, 1 fragment 05 x 1.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0349)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0350, 1 fragment 10.5 x 4 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0350)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0351, 1 fragment 04 x 9.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0351)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0352.01, 3 fragments 03.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0352.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0352.02, 3 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0352.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0352.03, 3 fragments 03 x 5.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0352.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0353, 1 fragment 06 x 4 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0353)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0354, 1 fragment 08 x 15.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0354)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0355, 1 fragment 10.5 x 4.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0355)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0356, 1 fragment 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0356)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0357, 1 fragment 10.5 x 4.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0357)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0358, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0358)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0359, 1 fragment 02 x 5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0359)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0360, 1 fragment 08.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0360)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0361, 1 fragment 06.5 x 7 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0361)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0362.01, 2 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0362.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0362.02, 2 fragments 10 x 4.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0362.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0363, 1 fragment 10 x 9.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0363)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0364, 1 fragment 03.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0364)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0365, 1 fragment 12.5 x 5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0365)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0366, 1 fragment 12 x 2 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0366)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0367, 1 fragment 05 x 4 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0367)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0368, 1 fragment 04 x 3 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0368)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0369, 1 fragment 08.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 6, Item P.NYU inv 0369)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0370, 1 fragment 06 x 4.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0370)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0371, 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0371)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0372, 1 fragment 09.5 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0372)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0374, 1 fragment 09.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0374)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0375, 1 fragment 05.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0375)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0376, 1 fragment 01 x 9 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0376)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0377, 1 fragment 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0377)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0378, 1 fragment 04 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0378)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0379, 1 fragment 12.5 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0379)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0380, 1 fragment 09 x 11 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0380)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0381, 1 fragment 10.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0381)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0382, 1 fragment 15.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0382)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0383, 1 fragment 16 x 12.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0383)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0384, 1 fragment 10 x 6 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0384)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0385, 1 fragment 13.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0385)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0386, 1 fragment 06 x 10 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0386)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0387, 1 fragment 06 x 8 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0387)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0388, 1 fragment 15 x 7.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0388)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0389, 1 fragment 12.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0389)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0390, 1 fragment 09 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0390)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0391, 1 fragment 06.5 x 8 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0391)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0392, 1 fragment 20 x 13 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0392)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0393, 1 fragment 09.5 x 5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0393)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0394, 1 fragment 17.5 x 3.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0394)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0395, 1 fragment 09 x 5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0395)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0396, 1 fragment 09.5 x 10 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0396)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0397, 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0397)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0398.01, 2 fragments 09.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0398.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0398.02, 2 fragments 00.5 x 2 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0398.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0399, 1 fragment 13.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0399)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.01, 1 fragment 20 x 10 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.02, 1 fragment 04 x 3 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.03, 1 fragment 03 x 1.5 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.04, 1 fragment 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.05, 1 fragment 02 x 02 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.06, 1 fragment 03 x 1 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.07, 1 fragment 05 x 0.5 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.08, 1 fragment 04 x 2 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0401, 1 fragment 08.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0401)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0402, 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0402)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0403.01, 1 fragment 11.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0403.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0403.02, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0403.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0404, 1 fragment 10.0 x 20.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0404)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0405.01, 1 fragment 06.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0405.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0405.02, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0405.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0406, 1 fragment 08.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0406)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0407, 1 fragment 13.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0407)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0408, 1 fragment 16.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0408)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0409, 1 fragment 07.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0409)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0410, 1 fragment 13.0 x 7.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0410)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0411, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0411)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0412, 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0412)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0413, 1 fragment 08.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0413)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0414, 1 fragment 14.5 x 7 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0414)